export const commonQuestions = [
  {
    buttonText: 'Trash',
    question: 'What is the schedule for trash and recycle?',
    answer:
      'The trash and recycle pickup schedule for Cheval West Community is as follows:\n\n' +
      '• **Trash pickup:** Monday and Thursday\n\n' +
      '• **Recycle pickup:** Monday\n\n' +
      '• **Yard waste pickup:** Monday\n\n' +
      'Please note that containers may only be left out on the day for the respective pickup and should be promptly returned from the street after collection to avoid potential fines.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where do I have to store my bins?',
    answer:
      'Trash cans and recycling containers must be stored out of view of the street and adjoining properties at all times, except on scheduled pickup days. Containers may be placed out at the curb very early in the morning on pickup days or after dark the evening before a scheduled pickup.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What are the trash pickup holidays?',
    answer:
      'There is no garbage, recycling, or yard waste collection on the following holidays:\n\n' +
      "• **New Year's Day (January 1)**\n\n" +
      '• **Martin Luther King, Jr. Day (Third Monday in January)**\n\n' +
      '• **Memorial Day (Last Monday in May)**\n\n' +
      '• **Juneteenth (June 19)**\n\n' +
      '• **Independence Day (July 4)**\n\n' +
      '• **Labor Day (First Monday in September)**\n\n' +
      '• **Thanksgiving Day (Fourth Thursday in November)**\n\n' +
      '• **Christmas Day (December 25)**\n\n' +
      'Regular collection resumes on the next scheduled collection day if your collection date falls on one of these holidays.'
  },
  {
    buttonText: 'Fence',
    question: 'Can I put up a fence on my property?',
    answer:
      'You can put up a fence on your property in Cheval West, but there are specific guidelines you must follow:\n\n' +
      '• **Approval Required:** You need to obtain written approval from the Architectural Review Committee before erecting any fence or wall.\n\n' +
      '• **Material and Design:** Only metal fences in the style of black or white wrought iron are permitted. The fence should consist of 5/8" to 1" pickets, 1" to 1.6" stringers, and 1x1" horizontal rails with spacing of 3" to 4".\n\n' +
      '• **Height Restrictions:** No fence or wall over four (4) feet in height is allowed, except for tennis courts and other special conditions approved by the Architectural Review Committee.\n\n' +
      '• **Location:** The fence must be erected entirely within your property line.\n\n' +
      'Please ensure you follow these guidelines and obtain the necessary approvals to avoid any issues.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the max height for a fence?',
    answer:
      'The maximum height for a fence in Cheval West is 4 feet, except for tennis courts and other special conditions as approved by the Architectural Review Committee.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What material can the fence be made out of?',
    answer:
      'Fences in Cheval West can be made out of the following materials:\n\n' +
      '• **Black or White Aluminum**\n\n' +
      '• **Black or White Wrought Iron**\n\n' +
      'Chain link fences, galvanized, vinyl coated, or otherwise treated chain link fences, as well as lattice (whether wood or PVC), are prohibited.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What color can my fence be?',
    answer: 'Fences in Cheval West can be either black or white.'
  },
  {
    buttonText: 'Flags',
    question: 'What are the rules for flags on my property?',
    answer:
      'In Florida, homeowners have specific rights regarding the display of flags on their property, as outlined in the Florida Statutes and community guidelines:\n\n' +
      '**Florida Statutes**\n\n' +
      '1. **Permitted Flags:** Homeowners may display up to two of the following flags, each not larger than 4 1/2 feet by 6 feet:\n' +
      '  - The United States flag\n' +
      '  - The official flag of the State of Florida\n' +
      '  - A flag representing the United States Army, Navy, Air Force, Marine Corps, Space Force, or Coast Guard\n' +
      '  - A POW-MIA flag\n' +
      '  - A first responder flag, which can honor various emergency and safety personnel.\n\n' +
      '2. **Flagpole Regulations:** Homeowners may erect a freestanding flagpole up to 20 feet high on their property, provided it does not obstruct sightlines at intersections or is not erected within an easement. The flagpole can display one official United States flag and one additional flag permitted under the above guidelines, with the additional flag being equal in size to or smaller than the United States flag. The flagpole and display must comply with all building codes, zoning setbacks, and other applicable regulations.\n\n' +
      '**Community Guidelines (Cheval West)**\n\n' +
      '1. **Flagpoles:** Approval is required for installing flagpoles. The flagpole must be appropriately sized for the lot and not exceed 20 feet in height. It must not obstruct sightlines at intersections or be erected within an easement.\n\n' +
      '2. **Flagstaffs:** No approval is required for a flagstaff attached to a house, provided it is under 6 feet in length, no greater than 2 inches in diameter, and is a neutral tone.\n\n' +
      '3. **Flag Display:** Homeowners may display up to two of the following flags, each not larger than 4 1/2 feet by 6 feet:\n' +
      '  - The United States flag\n' +
      '  - The official flag of the State of Florida\n' +
      '  - A flag representing the United States Army, Navy, Air Force, Marine Corps, Space Force, or Coast Guard\n' +
      '  - A POW-MIA flag\n' +
      '  - A first responder flag.\n\n' +
      '4. **Maintenance:** Flags, flagpoles, and flagstaffs must be maintained in good condition. Flags that are frayed, dilapidated, worn out, tattered, or faded must be removed and not displayed unless repaired or replaced. Proper lighting is encouraged for displaying the American Flag on a permanent flagpole.\n\n' +
      'These rules ensure that homeowners can display flags respectfully while adhering to community standards and legal requirements.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What types of flags can I install?',
    answer:
      'According to the Florida Statutes and community guidelines, you are allowed to display the following types of flags:\n\n' +
      '1. United States Flag: You may display one portable, removable United States flag in a respectful manner.\n\n' +
      '2. State of Florida Flag: The official flag of the State of Florida.\n\n' +
      '3. Military Flags: Flags representing the United States Army, Navy, Air Force, Marine Corps, Space Force, or Coast Guard.\n\n' +
      '4. POW-MIA Flag: A flag honoring prisoners of war and those missing in action.\n\n' +
      '5. First Responder Flags: Flags that recognize and honor the service of law enforcement officers, firefighters, paramedics, emergency medical technicians, correctional officers, 911 public safety telecommunicators, advanced practice registered nurses, licensed practical nurses, registered nurses, and persons participating in a statewide urban search and rescue program.\n\n' +
      'Additionally, you may erect a freestanding flagpole no more than 20 feet high on your property, provided it does not obstruct sightlines at intersections and is not erected within or upon an easement. You can display one official United States flag and one other flag permitted under the guidelines mentioned above.'
  },
  {
    question: 'What are the rules for flag poles?',
    answer:
      'In Florida, homeowners have specific rights regarding the display of flags on their property, as outlined in the Florida Statutes and community guidelines:\n\n' +
      '**Florida Statutes**\n\n' +
      '1. **Permitted Flags:** Homeowners may display up to two of the following flags, each not larger than 4 1/2 feet by 6 feet:\n' +
      '- The United States flag\n' +
      '- The official flag of the State of Florida\n' +
      '- A flag representing the United States Army, Navy, Air Force, Marine Corps, Space Force, or Coast Guard\n' +
      '- A POW-MIA flag\n' +
      '- A first responder flag, which can honor various emergency and safety personnel.\n\n' +
      '2. **Flagpole Regulations:** Homeowners may erect a freestanding flagpole up to 20 feet high on their property, provided it does not obstruct sightlines at intersections or is not erected within an easement. The flagpole can display one official United States flag and one additional flag permitted under the above guidelines, with the additional flag being equal in size to or smaller than the United States flag. The flagpole and display must comply with all building codes, zoning setbacks, and other applicable regulations.\n\n' +
      '**Community Guidelines (Cheval West)**\n\n' +
      '1. **Flagpoles:** Approval is required for installing flagpoles. The flagpole must be appropriately sized for the lot and not exceed 20 feet in height. It must not obstruct sightlines at intersections or be erected within an easement.\n\n' +
      '2. **Flagstaffs:** No approval is required for a flagstaff attached to a house, provided it is under 6 feet in length, no greater than 2 inches in diameter, and is a neutral tone.\n\n' +
      '3. **Flag Display:** Homeowners may display up to two of the following flags, each not larger than 4 1/2 feet by 6 feet:\n' +
      '- The United States flag\n' +
      '- The official flag of the State of Florida\n' +
      '- A flag representing the United States Army, Navy, Air Force, Marine Corps, Space Force, or Coast Guard\n' +
      '- A POW-MIA flag\n' +
      '- A first responder flag.\n\n' +
      '4. **Maintenance:** Flags, flagpoles, and flagstaffs must be maintained in good condition. Flags that are frayed, dilapidated, worn out, tattered, or faded must be removed and not displayed unless repaired or replaced. Proper lighting is encouraged for displaying the American Flag on a permanent flagpole.\n\n' +
      'These rules ensure that homeowners can display flags respectfully while adhering to community standards and legal requirements.'
  },
  {
    question: 'Can I display political flags?',
    answer:
      'Yes, you can display political flags. According to the Florida Statutes, homeowners are allowed to display up to two portable, removable flags, each not larger than 4 1/2 feet by 6 feet, which can include political flags, as long as they are displayed in a respectful manner. Additionally, the Cheval West community guidelines do not specifically prohibit political flags, but they do require that all flags be properly attached to either a flagpole or flagstaff and be properly displayed and maintained.'
  },
  {
    question: 'When is the next CDD board meeting?',
    answer:
      'The next board meeting is scheduled for Thursday, August 15, 2024, at 10:30 AM. It will be held at the Cheval Golf and Country Club, located at 4310 Cheval Boulevard, Lutz, Florida.'
  }
]
